[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
That's it.
Raise your hand.
Good. Love that.
Over here.
Beautiful.
Good.
Let's shoot one backlit.
One from the back.
Hello?
(Can't you hear the phone ringing?)
(Dad needs a fourth.)
(Get back here.)
I'm in the storeroom.
They need these photos ASAP.
I'm working late to finish them.
(Develop them after the game.)
(Stop calling.)
(Hurry! We're drinking.)
(Come on! Hurry!)
(Be here in 30 minutes.)
(I already told Dad.)
Fine.
(My Song.)
(Come on!)
(Hurry!)
=Ren Yu=
(Adapted from Lei Mi's novel Ren Yu)
=Episode 18=
Three Dots.
Pung.
Dad.
I'm back.
Zhou, you're back.
We needed a fourth.
Play already.
Quit stalling.
Okay.
Seven Bamboo.
Two Dots.
Want it?
No.
Me too.
One Bamboo.
Pass?
Pass.
Sorry, Dad.
I'm late.
Five Bamboo.
Kong.
I just discarded it.
Dad.
I'm heading up to rest.
Three Bamboo.
Eight Dots.
Six Dots.
Come on.
7 Characters.
I'm ready.
You're on a roll today.
Only you have a kong.
The food's cold.
I'll heat it up.
Okay.
I'm not going over there.
You shouldn't eat it cold.
Bad for your stomach.
So fake.
Then
I won't interfere.
Eat it cold if you want.
It's fine.
Then eat here.
The floor's cold.
Put on your slippers.
I haven't forgotten your mom.
And I do love you.
I remember one birthday as a kid.
You begged for a birthday cake.
But your mom and I had just
scraped together your tuition.
We had nothing left for a cake.
I wasn't being considerate.
I feel like I failed you.
Once I started making money,
I tried to give you the best,
everything you wanted,
right or wrong,
and fix every problem for you.
But I really
don't know what to do anymore.
If you don't want to go abroad,
from now on,
I
won't force you anymore.
Whenever you want me around,
I'll be here.
Can
you
forgive me?
Ma Dongchen.
Yeah?
I'm hungry. Heat up the food.
Okay.
Ow.
Sorry.
Scissors.
How is it?
What?
Don't you look good?
Good.
Yeah, handsome.
Hello?
(Bro.)
(They found another body.)
Another one?
(Earlier today.)
(I just heard.)
That old man Gu Hao took them there?
(Yeah.)
When?
Okay.
Got it.
Found this in Na's drawer.
Guess which new admirer's it's from.
Not that guy next door, right?
No way.
Too ugly for you?
Could it be Yang Le?
Na's in love again!
Open it.
Okay.
Time for the big reveal.
What'd Yang Le get you?
Place your bets!
Get out.
(You and your father)
(killed someone together.)
(She could've survived.)
(You got her killed.)
(I have proof of what you did.)
(Have 3,000 yuan ready.)
(4:00 p.m.)
(Old Town, Xinhu Street,)
(in the first trash can.)
(Remember,)
(call the cops,)
(you and your dad are finished.)
(Want me to buy you new white sneakers?)
(Let's go!)
(Here comes the Little Mermaid!)
(The prettiest Little Mermaid!)
(You?)
(The Little Mermaid?)
(As if.)
(Stay away from me!)
(Help!)
(Stay back!)
(Don't come any closer!)
2,000.
2,100.
Hello?
(Hey, Na.)
(The teacher saw you leave.)
(She asked me to check on you.)
(Are you feeling sick?)
(Want me to call you in sick?)
Okay.
(Okay.)
(I'll tell Ms. Wang.)
Wait.
Doesn't your family
run a shop on the old street?
(Yeah.)
(Why?)
Any place there that buys gold?
(Yeah, by our shop.)
Take me there.
Now. Take me there now.
(2-Yuan Shop)
Here.
A 2-yuan shop?
(Gold & Silver)
Sir?
(Top Prices for Gold)
Sorry. Sir?
Sir?
Coming.
What is it?
What are you paying for gold?
70 yuan a gram.
Don't try to rip us off.
It's over 100 yuan a gram out there.
Kid,
retail and buyback aren't the same.
If you don't know,
don't act like you do.
Sell or get out.
Come on.
That's way too low.
Sir,
I live right next door,
at Xiaosong Fruit Shop.
You know my parents, right?
My dad looks just like me.
Square face, kinda chubby.
How about 85 yuan?
You haggle like this over fruit too?
Market rate
is 70 yuan across the board.
Go to some shady dealer,
and you might
get even less.
What do we do?
I can take you somewhere else.
Fine. 70 yuan.
Cash.
Tell me about your job.
(Chaobei Aluminum Co., Ltd.)
When'd you rent it?
March last year.
You said earlier
the place you rent
isn't that close to work, right?
I'm planning to quit soon.
I've got a new job.
It means lots of travel,
so I moved closer to the station.
Right.
So,
the two of them were there
for over a month.
This bike?
He dropped it off last night.
Look.
Look what he did to it.
I've reached almost everyone.
Two are out of town.
I'll finish today.
Then eat up.
Fill up.
Then keep going.
Sir?
Mr. Zhou.
Is my stuff here?
Recognize him?
He had blood drawn here before.
(Woman Found in Sewer)
(New Weihong Canal Victim?)
(Popular Film)
Found it.
- Thanks.
- Zhou Xijie.
Sure.
Looking for you.
And here you are.
You are...
Police.
Relax.
We're working a case.
You're on our interview list.
Anything I can help with?
No.
Just a few questions.
Don't you work at the Culture Center?
What brings you here?
(Public Phone Booth / Newsstand)
There's an English recitation contest.
They asked me to coach them.
That's a long way from your place.
Over 40 minutes by bike.
I drive.
That's convenient.
How's that place you're renting?
Pretty good.
Good layout, good price.
Just curious.
I'm looking to move too.
I like that area.
Mainly because
there's a direct bus to work.
Officer,
if that's all, I should...
Class is about to start.
Sorry to bother you.
Go ahead.
Sir.
Thanks.
Sure.
Mr. Zhou.
That movie poster you wanted...
the one with Anth... something.
Anthony Hopkins.
Yes, him!
I found it.
Is this the one?
Yeah, that's it.
Thanks.
People buying magazines now
don't even want the posters.
You can have them all.
Thanks.
Sure.
What movie is this, Mr. Zhou?
Best Picture a couple years ago.
It's for
collection?
And study.
I should go.
A man of culture.
(Chaobei Vocational High School)
We've interviewed so many,
but few fully fit the profile.
Cheng, you got lucky.
Most on my list fit it.
That's a lot of legwork.
Look. Li Xiangdong.
Department store cashier.
Owns a car.
Looks clean-cut,
talks real polite.
Offered me a ride to the next guy.
No joke,
I almost got in.
That's a long way from your place.
Over 40 minutes by bike.
I drive.
Come on,
these are basic criteria.
Lots of people will fit them.
Look.
Feng Ziqiang.
College grad.
PR at the meat plant.
He wasn't even at work when I went.
He was asleep in his dorm.
Don't you work at the Culture Center?
What brings you here?
There's an English recitation contest.
They asked me to coach them.
And
this one.
Wang Tao.
Single.
Folks live back home.
Lives alone in company housing.
So he's got his own place.
How's that place you're renting?
Pretty good.
Good layout, good price.
Other criteria?
He fit those too?
Like
living away from family.
Yes.
And
any collecting habits.
Those, I think,
fit better
with the killer's deviant behavior.
It's for collection?
And study.
Call Du.
Call the provincial lab.
Test Zhou Xijie's blood first.
Go, go.
Sir, both tables are paid up.
Let's go.
Go.
(Taiping Gate)
Morning, Ms. Wang.
Morning, Mr. Zhou.
Everyone, line up.
Where's Ma Na?
Where did she go?
Know where she went?
How would I know?
Today's our final rehearsal.
I'll ask again.
Where's Ma Na?
Mr. Zhou.
Ma Na took the day off.
Took the day off?
Who approved it?
Keep going.
(Trash Can)
(I'll always be watching you.)
(What is true revenge?)
(Making those you hate suffer?)
(Su Lin's Diary)
Piled one upon the other,
would not reach from the ground
beneath to the surface
of the water above.
It's very very deep. So deep.
What?
Mr. Zhou, Ma Na's back.
Today's our final rehearsal.
You know that?
And you still show up late?
You have absolutely
no team spirit.
Someone like you
doesn't deserve the lead,
much less the Little Mermaid.
What's wrong with him?
Enough.
Ma Na, get back in line.
What a weirdo.
Na just left like that.
Ask her later?
Go ahead.
She's back.
Ma Na.
Na.
Keep going.
What now?
Zhao Lingling. Song Shuang.
Far out at ocean,
the water is as blue
as the petals of a cornflower,
and as clear as...
Gu.
I'm here.
Give me a hand.
(File Envelope)
Tai Wei asked me to give you this.
I brought the kid
some clothes and shoes,
and some toiletries.
Did you find her?
I'm talking to you.
Moving stuff?
This guy...
I'm asking you.
Say something.
You look out of it.
Did you find her?
Are you gonna answer me?
I found her.
Where is she?
I found where Su Lin was living.
Living?
If I hadn't left yesterday,
if I'd stayed there,
I might've seen her.
I could've brought her home.
Where'd you go?
After I took you home,
I followed Wu's map
and went back down.
I followed the route on the map.
We found a room.
I went inside.
Su Lin's clothes were there,
and her backpack.
I'm sure she'd been
living there all this time.
How was I supposed to know?
While we were waiting,
Jiang Ting's mom had low blood sugar.
Her mom went with you?
As I was going down
at Culture Square,
her mom was there.
She'd promised Jiang Ting
she'd find Su Lin.
So I let her come with me.
I told her her blood sugar was low.
Go home.
I'd stay and wait.
She wouldn't. She insisted on staying.
Finally, I knew she couldn't stay.
I couldn't let her get hurt down there.
So I took her home.
Once I got her home,
I came right back.
But when I entered the room,
gone.
Su Lin's clothes I'd just seen,
her backpack...
all gone.
Everything connected to her
was gone.
Cleared out.
She moved?
I don't know.
I don't know if she moved.
Then where could she be?
She's just a kid.
If she got out of the sewer herself,
wouldn't she go home?
Yeah.
So I thought,
maybe she couldn't get home before,
but made it back now.
So I rushed back.
Know why
I waited there all night?
I was afraid I'd fall asleep,
miss her coming in,
and miss her again.
And
the sewer.
Where she was staying,
I'm sure two people lived there.
Then maybe
someone be holding her?
No, no.
Held her?
Kidnapped?
Would a kidnapper care about clothes?
Let her wash them and pack her bag?
And that room was spotless.
You mean she had a friend down there?
I don't know if they were friends.
But what we do know is
there's a killer down there.
The bodies were found
far from where she lived.
Could that one be the killer?
How's Su Lin tied to the killer?
No. This is too dangerous.
Did you call Tai Wei?
I forgot.
Hello? Tai Wei?
(Gu.)
(I found out what you asked.)
What was it?
(That security company)
(that hired you to train.)
Security company?
What?
(It's backed by Zhongyu Construction.)
Zhongyu Construction?
The one here in Chaobei?
(Yeah.)
(A top local company.)
Got it.
(Okay.)
(Mr. Ma / Unknown Boss
Zhongyu Owner)
(Capt. Li / Employed)
(Dingsheng Crew
Zhongyu Construction)
I need to find Tai Wei.
Right now.
Dongchen.
Never came out all night.
A woman went in this morning.
Okay. Got it.
Get some sleep.
I'm off, then.
Go on home.
Okay.
Don't worry.
Go.
Mr. Gu.
Ma Dongchen.
Mr. Ma.
Big boss like you
waiting here for me?
Something up?
Well.
I've got a personal matter.
I'd like your advice on.
Got a minute?
A quick chat.
I should've
invited you somewhere nicer
for tea,
but it's urgent,
and I wanted some privacy.
I've been a cop all these years.
Never taken a dime.
Mr. Gu,
friends can help each other out.
Nothing wrong with that.
Don't.
We're not that close.
And we're not friends.
If you have something to say,
say it.
Fine.
Then
let me tell you a story.
There was a man
who happened to notice
his neighbor's daughter
hadn't come home for days.
So he searched everywhere.
But the girl
had just gone away to school.
Life's funny.
You meet someone,
become neighbors,
and before you know it,
they move away.
Maybe you never see them again.
My point is,
we should mind our own business.
That's best.
Don't you think?
You like stories, Mr. Ma.
Then here's one for you.
There was a girl.
Let's call her
Girl A.
She had a classmate.
Let's call her
Girl C.
The two
got into an argument.
Girl A
shoved
Girl C into a sewer.
Girl A's father
tried to cover up her crime.
He went to Girl C's family
and made a deal,
negotiated terms,
paid them,
got their son registered,
and into elementary school.
To stop them looking for her,
he threatened them.
He even
crippled her father's leg.
And that's not all.
He locked the man looking for her
down in a manhole.
He even
tried to use money
to make every problem go away.
Quite a story.
But to be fair,
it's a little too dramatic.
Sounds made up.
Like the mysteries my daughter reads.
But even mysteries
need evidence, don't they?
You know, the police could easily
check the shoeprints and fingerprints
by the well, right?
And that shoeprint
was unusual.
This is a small town.
People who can afford imported shoes?
Not many.
Being a dad isn't easy.
For his daughter,
he must've been terrified.
He panicked
and made a mistake.
Take that manhole cover.
You piled all those bricks on it.
I almost died down there.
For his daughter's sake,
he panicked.
He was cornered.
Had no choice.
No other way.
Really?
The child makes one mistake,
then the father makes another,
covering it up for her.
He goes further,
keeps making it worse.
Is that really helping his child?
I've been a cop a long time.
One thing I've learned,
never think you'll get away with it.
A kid's mistake can be fixed.
But if a father gets tunnel vision,
and turns to crime,
there's no turning back.
That's how you ruin your child's life.
Mr. Ma.
I have an old friend.
I can take you to see him right now.
Tell him what's on your mind.
Maybe there's still
a way out.
Let's go.
I'll drive.
I know the way.
Okay.
(These materials must arrive tomorrow.)
(The site's waiting.)
(Find a way.)
(Pay more if needed.)
(It's fine.)
Get in my way,
and I'll make you disappear.
Why do you keep
targeting my daughter?
Targeting her...
=Ren Yu=
(Next Time...)
Go!
If you ever bully Jiang Ting again,
I won't let it slide.
Got it?
Anyone?
Pack your things. Now.
We fly to Los Angeles tonight.
Did something happen?
Listen.
This is a murder case.
Think carefully.
You can tell me here,
or back at the station.
The provincial lab says
Zhou Xijie's DNA
doesn't match the killer's.
He's not even type A.
♪Darkness♪
♪Spreads like ink♪
♪Lost♪
♪Eyes search the shadows♪
♪So many♪
♪stories hide in life's corners♪
♪I remember♪
♪Every joy and sorrow♪
♪Till a dazzling beam breaks through♪
♪I know that light is salvation♪
♪The torn night♪
♪Declares an end♪
♪And loneliness, in this moment♪
♪Fades into nothing♪
♪I'll fight free♪
♪Of the darkness♪
♪And break the chains of fate♪
♪Let me touch the blue sky above♪
♪That light♪
♪Suddenly falls♪
♪Saving all my broken pieces♪
♪Till a dazzling beam breaks through♪
♪I know that light is salvation♪
♪The torn night♪
♪Declares an end♪
♪And loneliness, in this moment♪
♪Fades into nothing♪
♪I'll fight free♪
♪Of the darkness♪
♪And break the chains of fate♪
♪Let me touch the blue sky above♪
♪That light suddenly falls♪
♪Saving all my broken pieces♪
♪It saves me♪